A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.9-SG 1.13 (A83-A87) FA479
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A 85), 1970-1985; 1.11; 74.4 Cubic Feet; 62 standard record storage boxes - Box R2242-R2302 and R2304.
  - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 120
    - Scholars - Kellerman, 1983-1984 (Box R2245)
    - Scholars - King, 1978-1980 1982-1984 (Box R2245)
    - Scholars - Kolko, 1981-1983 (Box R2245)
    - Scholars - Kraehe, 1982-1984 (Box R2245)
    - Scholars - Kuhn, 1982-1984 (Box R2245)
    - Scholars - Lambert, 1981-1983 (Box R2245)
    - Scholars - Lelyveld (did not go), 1979 (Box R2245)
    - Scholars - Leon, Carlos A., 1982-1983 (Box R2246)
    - Scholars - Lewis, Richard W.B., 1982-1984 (Box R2246)
    - Scholars - McMillan, Carl H., 1981-1984 (Box R2246)
    - Scholars - McPhee, John a., 1982-1983 (Box R2246)
    - Scholars - Malamud, Bernard, 1982-1984 (Box R2246)
    - Scholars - Martin, Jay, 1982-1984 (Box R2246)
    - Scholars - Marx, Leo, 1982-1984 (Box R2246)
    - Scholars - Mayor, Heather D., 1979-1983 (Box R2246)
    - Scholars - Miedzyrzecki, A., 1981-1984 (Box R2246)
    - Scholars - Miles, Margaret R., 1982-1983 (Box R2246)
    - Scholars - Minear, Paul S., 1982-1984 (Box R2246)
    - Scholars - Nowotny, Thomas, 1982-1983 (Box R2246)
    - Scholars - Oakes, Rodney, 1982-1984 (Box R2246)
    - Scholars - Peden, Margaret S., 1981-1984 (Box R2246)
    - Scholars - Perlman, Mark, 1981-1983 (Box R2246)
    - Scholars - Perlongo, Daniel J., 1982-1983 (Box R2246)
    - Scholars - Robinson, Kenneth L., 1982-1983 (Box R2246)
    - Scholars - Rostow, Walt Whitman, 1982-1984 (Box R2246)
    - Scholars - Rowley, Charles D., 1982-1984 (Box R2246)
    - Scholars - Ruttan, Vernon W., 1980-1984 (Box R2246)
    - Scholars - Saward, Ernest W., 1981-1984 (Box R2247)
    - Scholars - Scanlan, James P., 1982-1983 (Box R2247)
    - Scholars - Schoultz, Lars, 1982-1983 (Box R2247)
    - Scholars - Segre, Dan Victor, 1981-1983 (Box R2247)
    - Scholars - Shaffer, Richard, 1982-1984 (Box R2247)
    - Scholars - Siegmeister, Elie, 1982-1984 (Box R2247)
    - Scholars - Silver, George A., 1982-1984 (Box R2247)
    - Scholars - Sinclair, Sir Ian, 1982-1983 (Box R2247)
    - Scholars - Singer, Jerome L., 1981-1983 (Box R2247)
    - Scholars - Stone, Robert, 1981-1983 (Box R2247)
    - Scholars - Stryk, Lucien, 1982-1983 (Box R2247)
    - Scholars - Swing, John T., 1982-1984 (Box R2247)
    - Scholars - Thurston, H. David, 1981-1984 (Box R2247)
    - Scholars - Treitler, Leo, 1982-1984 (Box R2247)
    - Scholars - Uttal, William R., 1982-1983 (Box R2247)
    - Scholars - Wang, In Kuen, 1981-1983 (Box R2247)
    - Scholars - White, Robert E., 1982-1983 (Box R2247)
    - Scholars - Witte, Ann Dryen, 1982-1983 1985 (Box R2247)
    - Scholars - Zwilich, Ellen Taaffe, 1982-1983 (Box R2247)
    - Selective Primary Health Care - Conference, 1982-1983 (Box R2247)
    - Sorghum Diseases Conference, 1982-1984 (Box R2247)
    - Stability in South and Southeast Asia - Conference, 1981-1982 (Box R2247)
    - State Power in China Conference, 1980-1983 (Box R2247)
    - Survey Research in Arab World Conference, 1982-1983 (Box R2248)
    - War and Society in East Central Europe - Conference, 1982-1983 (Box R2248)
    - Welfare State: Dangers for Women Conference, 1982-1983 (Box R2248)
  - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy, 150
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Connecticut, 208
      - Olsen, Randall J., 1980-1983 (Box R2248)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Louisiana, 221
      - Newman, John, 1980-1984 (Box R2248)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Massachusetts, 224
      - Repetto, Robert, 1980-1983 (Box R2248)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Missouri, 228
      - Hicks, W. Whitney, 1980-1984 (Box R2248)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Rhode Island, 244
      - Fosu, Gabriel Basil, 1981-1983 (Box R2248)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Wisconsin, 255
      - Palloni, A., 1981-1984 (Box R2248)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Peru, 331
      - Universidad Peruana Cayetano Heredia - Mortality differentials conference, 1982-1984 (Box R2249)
  - Demographic Evaluation Projects, 151
    - Demographic Evaluation Projects - Michigan, 225
      - University of Michigan - Mexican migration to United States, 1980-1983 (Box R2249)
    - Demographic Evaluation Projects - Colombia, 311
      - Corporación Centro Regional de Población - Demography, 1978 1981-1984 (Box R2249)
    - Demographic Evaluation Projects - 724, 724
      - Chilivumbo, Alifeyo, 1981-1983 (Box R2249)
    - Demographic Evaluation Projects - Liberia, 759
      - University of Liberia - Fertility regulation, 1981-1982 (Box R2249)
  - CILCA, 165
    - (Food Corps Programs), 1978-1983 (Box R2256)
  - 172
    - Chinese Academy of Medical Sciences - Antifertility peptides, 1982-1983 (Box R2256)
    - Chinese Academy of Sciences - Reproductive endocrinology (also 6[unreadable]), 1981-1984 (Box R2256)
    - National Institute of Nutrition Salvador Zubirán - FSH microheterogeneity, 1983-1985 (Box R2257)
    - University of Ibadan - Membrane physiology, 1980-1983 (Box R2257)
    - University of Lagos - Gonadotropin, 1980-1983 (Box R2257)
  - Research Fellowship for Minority-Group Scholars, 175
    - Research Fellowship for Minority-Group Scholars - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Allen, Walter R., 1982-1984 (Box R2257)
      - Blake, John H., 1982-1984 (Box R2257)
      - Brown, Frank, 1979-1982 (Box R2257)
      - Camarillo, Albert, 1982-1983 (Box R2257)
      - Champagne, Duane, 1982-1984 (Box R2257)
      - Cole, Lorraine T., 1981-1984 (Box R2257)
      - De la Garza, Rudolfo O., 1979-1982 (Box R2257)
      - Dong, Lorraine, 1982-1984 (Box R2257)
      - Fry, Gladys-Marie, 1982-1984 (Box R2257)
      - Hare, Bruce R., 1982-1984 (Box R2257)
      - Jefferson, Francine E., 1982-1983 (Box R2257)
      - McLemore, Leslie B., 1982-1984 (Box R2257)
      - Myers, Samuel L., Jr, 1979-1980 (Box R2257)
      - Neighbors, Harold W., 1981-1983 (Box R2257)
      - Ruiz, Richard, 1982-1985 (Box R2258)
      - Sanchez, Marta, 1982-1983 (Box R2258)
      - Simpson, Gwyned, 1981-1984 (Box R2258)
      - Stall worth, Lamont E., 1982-1984 (Box R2258)
      - Stanfield, John H. II, 1981-1983 (Box R2258)
      - Sue, Stanley, 1982-1984 (Box R2258)
      - Walton, Hanes, Jr., 1979-1982 (Box R2258)
      - Wilkerson, Margaret, 1982-1984 (Box R2258)
  - U.S. Immigration and Refugee Project, 181
    - Fagen, Patricia Weiss, 1982-1985 (Box R2258)
    - Reimers, David, 1982-1984 (Box R2258)
  - Utilization of Fragile Environments and Marginal Lands, 190
    - National Agricultural Research Institute - Valverde S., Carlos, 1980-1984 (Box R2258)
    - North Carolina State University - Perry, Jesse, 1978-1983 (Box R2259)
    - Utilization of Fragile Environments and Marginal Lands - CIAT, 110
      - Amazon Basin, 1981 1983-1984 (Box R2259)
  - 195
    - International Training & Research in Clinical Epidemiology (file appears to be incomplete), 1980 (Box R2259)
    - Shanghai First Medical College - Health Records, 1980-1983 (Box R2259)
  - 199
    - Beacon Hill Research Foundation - Gossypol, 1982-1984 (Box R2259)
    - Chinese Academy of Medical Sciences - Gossypol acetic acid, 1981-1983 (Box R2259)
    - Population Council - Gossypol, 1981-1983 (Box R2259)
    - University of Michigan - Gossypol, 1981-1984 (Box R2259)
  - United States, 200
    - Agricultural Development Council - Social Science, 1982-1984 (Box R2259)
    - American Assembly - American Political Parties Conference, 1981-1984 (Box R2259)
    - Atlanta University Center - Planning and development, 1979-1983 (Box R2259)
    - Brookings Institution - Voluntary sector, 1982-1984 (Box R2260)
    - Citizen's Committee for Immigration Reform, 1981-1984 (Box R2260)
    - City University of New York - Summer high school program, 1982-1984 (Box R2260)
    - Columbia University - Women and income in the third world conference, 1981-1983 (Box R2260)
    - Denver - Education - Administrative interns, 1975-1980 (Box R2260)
    - Equity Policy Center - Women's roles on small farms conference, 1982-1984 (Box R2260)
    - Flexner, James T., 1979-1984 (Box R2260)
    - Harvard University - Intergenerational mobility, 1980-1984 (Box R2260)
    - Howard University - Development officers training, 1979-1981 (Box R2260)
    - International Fertilizer Development Center - Hansen, 1980-1984 (Box R2260)
    - Lawyers' Committee for Civil Rights Under Law - Mississippi interns, 1973-1981 1983 (Box R2261)
    - Lawyers' Committee for Civil Rights Under Law - North Carolina municipal services, 1979-198[?] (Box R2261)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - International nutrition center, 1972-1984 (Box R2261)
    - Memphis - Education - Leadership development, 1974-1981 (Box R2261)
    - Mexican American Cultural Center - Youth leadership, 1981-1984 (Box R2261)
    - Mexican American Legal Defense and Education Fund - Voter law policy, 1980-1984 (Box R2261)
    - Millsaps College - Mississippi Freedom summer anniversary, 1979-1980 (Box R2262)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People - Voter registration, 1982-1985 (Box R2262)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People - Voting law, 1980-1984 (Box R2262)
    - National Association for the Southern Poor, 1976-1984 (Box R2262)
    - National Congress of American-Indians - Textbooks, 1981-1984 (Box R2262)
    - National Council on Crime and Delinquency - Community crime prevention, 1982-1983 1991 (Box R2262)
    - National Executive Service Corps, 1978-1984 (Box R2263)
    - National Institute for Work and Learning - Fast food industry and employment, 1981-1984 1991 (Box R2263)
    - Notional Puerto Rican Coalition, Inc. - [unreadable], 1981-1984 (Box R2263)
    - National Urban League - Busing/school desegregation conference, 1982-1983 (Box R2263)
    - New York University - Law internships, 1978-1981 (Box R2263)
    - Puerto Rican Legal Defense and Education Fund - Voting rights, 1982-1983 (Box R2263)
    - Rockefeller University - "Sharp compassion", 1980-1983 (Box R2263)
    - Southern Education Foundation - Black colleges, 1979-1981 1984 (Box R2264)
    - Southern Regional Council - Voting rights, 1980-1984 (Box R2264)
    - Southwest Voter Registration Education Project - Chicano survey, 1980-1984 (Box R2264)
    - University of Chicago - Foundations and public policy, 1977-1982 (Box R2264)
    - University of Florida - Agriculture, change and human values conference, 1982-1984 (Box R2264)
    - University of Notre Dame - Hesburgh papers, 1982 (Box R2264)
    - University of Pennsylvania - Black law journal, 1981 (Box R2264)
    - University of South Alabama - At large election procedures, 1981-1983 (Box R2265)
    - University of Virginia - Law of the sea, 1978-1982 1984 (Box R2265)
    - University of Wisconsin - Cross national disability policy study, 1981-1984 (Box R2265)
    - Urban Institute - Employment affirmative action, 1981-1983 (Box R2265)
    - Urban Institute - Job seekers and openings, 1981-1984 (Box R2265)
    - Urban Institute - Minorities and women federal employment, 1981-1984 (Box R2265)
    - Urban Institute - Women's lifetime earnings, 1983-1984 (Box R2266)
    - Virginia State College - Public administration training, 1975-1985 (Box R2266)
    - Voter Education Project, Inc. - Conferences, 1981-1984 (Box R2266)
    - United States - Medical Sciences, A
      - Beth Israel Hospital, Boston - Bibliographies retrievals, 1982 1984 (Box R2266)
      - Center for Disease Control - Family planning evaluation - Akhter, 1980-1984 (Box R2266)
      - Center for disease Control - Family planning evaluation - Huezo Toledo, 1980-1983 (Box R2266)
      - Center for Disease Control - Family planning evaluation - Moses, 1981-1983 (Box R2266)
      - Center for Public Resources, Inc. - Tropical disease, 1980-1982 (Box R2266)
      - Center for Public Resources, Inc. - Tropical disease & suppl. material, 1978-1979 (Box R2267)
      - Columbia University - Family planning training, 1979-1984 (Box R2268)
      - Cornell University - Geographic medicine planning, 1978-1981 (Box R2268)
      - Ellner, Jerrold J., 1980-1985 (Box R2268)
      - Garcia-Blanco, Mariano A., 1982 1984 (Box R2268)
      - Harvard University - Walsh, Julia, 1980-1983 (Box R2263)
      - New York University - Biomedical research, 1982-1984 (Box R2268)
      - Pan American Health Organization - Regional medical library, 1979-1984 (Box R2268)
      - Rockefeller University - Leprosy, 1982-1984 (Box R2268)
      - Tufts University - Health indicators conference, 1979-1985 (Box R2268)
      - University of California - Metabolic pathways, San Francisco, 1981-1985 (Box R2268)
      - University of Hawaii - Vaccine, 1979-1984 (Box R2268)
      - University of Maryland - Growth of children, 1982-1984 (Box R2268)
      - Yale University - Ticks, 1980-1984 (Box R2269)
    - United States - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, D
      - Agricultural Development Council - Panayotou, 1980-1984 (Box R2269)
      - Cornell University - Pest control, 1977-1982 (Box R2269)
      - Cornell University - Phytoalexins, 1977-1984 (Box R2269)
      - Harvard University - McPherson, 1981-1984 (Box R2269)
      - Kansas State University - Protoplasts, 1978-1983 (Box R2269)
      - Louisiana State University - Soil redox, 1980-1984 (Box R2269)
      - University of Arizona - Halophytes, 1978-1984 (Box R2269)
      - University of California - Genetic Conference, Davis, 1982-1983 (Box R2269)
      - University of California - Pest Resistance, Davis, 1977-1984 (Box R2270)
      - University of Colorado - Phytoalexins, 1977-1984 (Box R2270)
      - University of Florida - Livestock Production Conference, 1981-1983 (Box R2270)
      - University of Minnesota - Maize, 1980-1984 (Box R2270)
      - University of Wisconsin - Lectins, 1976-1983 (Box R2270)
      - Washington State University - Hemoparasitic diseases, 1979-1984 (Box R2270)
    - United States - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Aley, Stephen B., 1981-1983 (Box R2270)
      - Gonzales-Peralta, Carlos, 1978-1984 (Box R2270)
      - Greve, Jeffrey M., 1980-1982 (Box R2270)
      - Hajduk, S.L., 1980-1983 (Box R2271)
      - Lam, David A., 1981-1983 (Box R2271)
      - Mensch, Barbara S., 1981-1984 (Box R2271)
      - Nothnagel, Eugene A., 1979-1983 (Box R2271)
    - United States - Population Sciences, P
      - American Society for Pharmacology & Experimental Therapeutics - Contraceptive drugs Conference, 1983-1984 (Box R2271)
      - Boston College - Bioethics of assisted rhythm, 1979-1984 (Box R2271)
      - Brandeis University - Pluralism study, 1981-1982 (Box R2271)
      - Cornell University - Guatemala data, 1983-1984 (Box R2271)
      - Cornell University - Monoclonal antibodies, 1982-1984 (Box R2271)
      - East Carolina University - Ovarian regulation, 1980-1983 (Box R2271)
      - East-West Center - Population trends in Southeast Asia conference, 1982-1983 (Box R2272)
      - Guttmacher Institute - Fertility control methods, 1981-1982 1984 (Box R2272)
      - Hertz, Roy, 1980-1982 1984 (Box R2272)
      - Lapham, Robert J., 1982 1984 (Box R2272)
      - Medical College of Wisconsin - Trophoblast neoplasms conf., 1981-1983 (Box R2272)
      - Mississippi Action for Community Education - Adolescent pregnancy, 1983-1984 (Box R2272)
      - Princeton University - Chinese fertility survey, 1983-1984 (Box R2272)
      - University of California - Glycoproteins, 1980-1983 (Box R2272)
      - University of Maryland - Inhibin-F secretion, 1979-1985 (Box R2272)
      - University of Michigan - World fertility survey analysis, 1983-1984 (Box R2272)
      - University of Pennsylvania - Oocyte growth, 1982-1984 (Box R2272)
    - United States - Humanities and Arts, R
      - American Academy of Arts & Sciences - Daedalus cultural literacy issue, 1980-1983 (Box R2272)
      - American Place Theatre - "Do Lord Remember Me", 1983-1984 (Box R2272)
      - Arts and Business Council - Conference, 1983-1984 (Box R2272)
      - Association of American Colleges - Women's college coalition, 1982-1984 (Box R2272)
      - Association of American Universities - Research universities conference, 1980-1983 (Box R2272)
      - Black Filmmaker Foundation, 1979-1983 (Box R2273)
      - Brooklyn College - Computer music, 1980-1984 (Box R2273)
      - Bryn Mawr College - Human studies conference, 1982-1983 (Box R2273)
      - Cabin Creek Center - Plant closings film, 1982-1985 (Box R2273)
      - California State University - Working women, 1974-1983 1985 (Box R2273)
      - Carter Family Memorial Music Center - Book, 1981-1983 (Box R2273)
      - Case Western Reserve University - History of aging conference, 1981-1984 (Box R2273)
      - Center for Southern Folklore - Beale Street history, 1982-1984 (Box R2273)
      - City University of New York - Graduate School - Ortega y Gasset conference, 1981-1984 (Box R2274)
      - Claremont University Center - African literature conference, 1981-1983 (Box R2274)
      - Columbia University - Human rights research, 1979-1984 (Box R2274)
      - Columbia University - Jay papers, 1978-1983 (Box R2274)
      - Columbia University - Polish oral history (rescinded), 1982-1983 (Box R2274)
      - Columbia University - Religious freedom conference, 1975-1985 (Box R2274)
      - Council for Basic Education - Television and education conference, 1981-1985 (Box R2274)
      - Dashow, J., 1981-1983 (Box R2274)
      - Diamond, David L., 1982-1984 (Box R2274)
      - Downtown Community Television Center, 1979-1980 1982-1984 (Box R2274)
      - East Carolina University - American music festival, 1980-1984 (Box R2274)
      - Emory University - Rethinking human rights conference, 1981-1984 (Box R2274)
      - Emshwiller, Ed, 1981-1983 (Box R2274)
      - Film Company - The Battle of Ole Miss, 1981-1982 1984 (Box R2274)
      - Fund for Arts and Science Films - "Vision of America", 1982-1984 (Box R2274)
      - Graduate Theological Union - New American Religious Movements, 1976-1984 (Box R2275)
      - Ho, Cordell, 1981-1982 1984 (Box R2275)
      - Howard University - Africa literature conference, 1981-1983 (Box R2275)
      - Independent Film Distribution and Marketing, 1980-1983 (Box R2275)
      - Institute for Research in History - Radicalism conference, 1979-1983 (Box R2275)
      - International Council for Educational Development - National council for foreign language, 1979-1983 1985 (Box R2276)
      - Jazzmobile, Inc., 1980-1983 (Box R2276)
      - Kozol, Jonathan, 1981-1984 (Box R2277)
      - Magic Theatre Inc. - American plays, 1983-1984 (Box R2277)
      - Marshall, Ingram D., 1981-1984 (Box R2277)
      - Museum of Holography, 1976-1984 (Box R2277)
      - National Alliance of Media Arts Centers, 1979-1984 (Box R2277)
      - National Humanities Faculty - Teaching of humanities, 1980-1983 (Box R2278)
      - New World Festival, Inc., 1981-1982 (Box R2278)
      - New York Council for the Humanities - Central America and the Caribbean conference, 1982-1983 (Box R2278)
      - New York University - Human rights conference, 1978-1983 (Box R2278)
      - New York University - Writers-at-work, 1978-1984 (Box R2278)
      - Northwestern University - American music festival, 1981-1983 (Box R2278)
      - Nunez, Victor, 1982-1984 (Box R2278)
      - Original Ballets Foundation, 1973-1984 (Box R2279)
      - Princeton University - Carter concert, 1981-1982 (Box R2279)
      - Queens College - Scope conference, 1982-1985 (Box R2279)
      - Reich Music Foundation, Inc., 1975-1976 1978-1984 (Box R2279)
      - Scripps College - Modernism conference, 1981-1983 (Box R2279)
      - Solaris Dance Theatre, 1982-1984 (Box R2279)
      - Subotnick, Morton, 1977-1984 (Box R2280)
      - Sundance Institute for Film and Television - Independent filmmakers, 1980-1984 (Box R2280)
      - Theatre, Inc. - New Phoenix Theatre - New works, 1978-1983 (Box R2280)
      - University of California - Social commitment, 1978-1984 (Box R2280)
      - University of Chicago - Creation and interpretation conference, 1981-1984 (Box R2280)
      - University of Chicago - Religion and western culture conf., 1982-1984 (Box R2280)
      - University of Minnesota - European studies/American research libraries conf., 1982-19[?] (Box R2280)
      - University of Tennessee - Medical ethics conference, 1979-1982 (Box R2280)
      - Wenner - Gren Foundation - Theatre and ritual symposium, 1980 1982-1984 (Box R2280)
      - Yale University - Ellington oral history, 1978-1984 (Box R2281)
      - Yale University - Teachers Institute, 1981-1984 (Box R2281)
    - United States - Social Sciences, S
      - Brandeis University - Youth practitioner's network, 1980-1984 (Box R2281)
      - Corporation for Public/Private Ventures - Youth unemployment, 1978-1982 (Box R2282)
      - Corporation for Public/Private ventures - Youth unemployment (suppl. material) (Box R2283)
      - National Bureau of Economic Research - Minority youth employment, 1978-1983 1985 (Box R2283)
      - Policy Studies Organization - Environmental policy, 1978-1982 1984 (Box R2284)
      - Rand Corporation - Civil Justice Institute, 1980-1985 (Box R2284)
      - University of Pennsylvania - Population studies, 1971-1980 (Box R2285)
  - Media Arts Centers, 259
    - (Media Arts Centers) (Minutes), 1981 (Box R2296)
    - Bay Area Video Coalition, 1980-1985 (Box R2296)
  - Fellowships in Admin, of Early Childhood and Exceptional Children Educational Programs, 267
    - Fellowships in Admin, of Early Childhood and Exceptional Children Educational Programs - California, 205
      - Chavez, John Maurice, 1978-1981 (Box R2296)
    - Fellowships in Admin, of Early Childhood and Exceptional Children Educational Programs - Illinois, 216
      - Evanston - Jackson, 1976-1977 1980 (Box R2296)
    - Fellowships in Admin, of Early Childhood and Exceptional Children Educational Programs - Minnesota, 226
      - Brady, Nelvia M., 1978-1982 (Box R2296)
    - Fellowships in Admin, of Early Childhood and Exceptional Children Educational Programs - South Dakota, 247
      - Miyasato, Stephen J., 1978-1981 (Box R2296)
  - U.S. Education - Administration & Finance Fellowships, 268
    - U.S. Education - Administration & Finance Fellowships - Fellowships, E
      - Johnson, Sharon D., 1977-1981 (Box R2296)
  - Equal Opportunity Project in Southern United States, 275
    - (Equal Opportunity Project in the Southern Region of the U.S.), 1974-1979 1981-1982 (Box R2296)
    - NAACP - Citizenship education, 1978-1979 1981 (Box R2296)
    - National Association for the Southern Poor - Fund raising, 1981-1982 (Box R2296)
    - Southern University - Rural development, 1976-1982 (Box R2296)
    - Tuskegee Institute - Goat production, 1976-1979 (Box R2297)
    - Tuskegee Institute - Small farmers, 1976-1982 (Box R2297)
    - Urban League of Greater Little Rock, Inc., 1977-1981 1983 (Box R2297)
    - Voter Education Project, Inc., 1977-1979 1981 (Box R2297)
  - Equal Opportunity Projects, 277
    - (Economic Opportunity Projects), 1979 1981-1982 (Box R2297)
    - Brandeis University - Youth employment impact, 1983-1984 (Box R2297)
    - Columbia University - Minority access and occupations, 1982-1983 (Box R2297)
    - King Center for Non-violent Social Change - Urban education, 1983-1984 (Box R2297)
    - Manpower Demonstration Research Corp. - Youth initiative, 1983-1985 (Box R2298)
  - Brazil, 305
    - University of Bahia - Donation of equipment, 1976-1983 (Box R2298)
    - Brazil - Social Sciences, S